本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
你觉得我很弱吗?
Am i looking weak to you?
"嘿 加勒特
"hey, Garrett,
你今天过的怎么样?"
how was your day?"
EVERYONE
这是正常人会说来打开话匣子的方式
That's how normal people start a conversation.
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
当我是管理人员的时候 我有权力
when i was management, i had power.
扫扫加微信
我当初为什么放弃呢?
Why did i give that up?
大家字幕组
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
我们当初裁员数量第一
We were number one in shrink reduction
dajiazimuzu
职工满意度垫底
And last in employee satisfaction.
这是我干的
I did that.
扫扫加微信
现在这个世界看起来真愚蠢
Now the world just seems dull or something.
dajiazimuzu
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
伙伴们
Guys?
好吧 要去医院了吗?
Okay. time to go to the hospital?
我不觉得我能撑到医院
I don't think i'm gonna make it to the hospital.
我只能在这生了
I think i'm having this baby here.
好吧好吧 那我们现在需要毛巾
Okay. We need towels.
谁去商店买点毛巾来啊!
Someone run to the store and buy some towels!
不不不 等等! 我们就是个商店啊!
No, wait! We're a store!
- 搞点毛巾来! - 这就去
- Get some towels! - On it.
你不能在店里面生孩子
You're not gonna have the baby in the store.
时间还多的呢 小夏
You have plenty of time, Chey.
而且这也许只是假临产现象
And it could be false labor.
你懂么? 这就是所谓的一个布拉克斯顿希克斯收缩
You know? that's called a braxton hicks contraction.
这孩子不能生在云九商店
this baby is not gonna be born in cloud 9.
也许这是布拉克斯顿希克斯收缩
Maybe it's braxton hicks.
好啦 我们知道啦 你知道这个术语布拉克斯顿希克斯收缩
Okay, we get it. You know the term braxton hicks.
你好棒哟！
We're all very impressed.
不 我只能在这生了
No, i'm having this baby here.
好的 就这样了!
Okay, this is it!
就这么办了!
This is happening!
我没任何感觉
I feel nothing.
注意 顾客们
Attention, shoppers.
你们中有医生...?
Is there a doctor in the...
开什么玩笑? 这可是云九商店
Who am i kidding? This is cloud 9.
你们谁是《实习医生格蕾》的忠实粉丝啊?
Anybody here watched a lot of "grey's anatomy?"
或者《护士当家》也可以啊?
Maybe "nurse jackie"?
《到拐点》就算了
Not "the knick."
毛巾 毛巾 毛巾
Towels. towels. towels.
让道!药剂师来了!
Move! Pharmacist coming through.
让一下 我需要空间
Step aside. I need room.
好了 夏安
All right, Cheyenne.
我需要你认真听我说话
I need you to listen to me here,
咱们一起面对
and we will get through this.
好 24小时之内
Now, in the last 24 hours,
你有没有服用任何需要让我知道的药物?
Have you taken any medication i need to know about.
只有一些胃药
Just some tums.
碳酸钙 没关系
Calcium carbonate. That's fine.
这个不会伤害宝宝
It's not gonna harm the baby.
好了
All right.
好吧 是 就这样了?
Okay, yeah. That's it?
嗯 对啊
Well, yeah.
我是个药剂师
I'm a pharmacist.
我又不知道怎么接生
I don't know how to deliver a baby.
多恶心
Gross.
但是 嗯 祝好运
But, um, good luck.
突如其来的考验
My training kicked in.
你们不用感谢我
You're welcome, everyone.
好的 这很好
Okay, that's good.
如果宫缩时间再长点 那就代表你...
If the contractions are longer, that means you're in...
真的要生了 所以我猜你现在是真的要生了
It's called active labor, so i guess you're in active labor.
我还是去准备东西吧
I'm gonna go get some stuff.
好的 我曾经给牛接生过
Okay, look. I took part in a cow birth once.
小牛死掉了 但是我学到了一些不该做的事情
The calf died, but i learned what not to do.
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no.
啊 不 是这个
Ah, no. yes.
我们要用到棉球吗?
Will we need cotton balls?
我还是拿点棉球吧
I'll get cotton balls.
不 不
No, no.
这个不错耶
Ooh, yes.
夏安 我想要你等等
Cheyenne, I want you to wait until
等你有无法阻挡的感觉的时候用力 好吗?
you have an uncontrollable urge to push, okay?
然后 你需要用尽全力往前推
And then, you're gonna bear down with all your strength
一次十秒钟左右 明白吗?
for ten seconds at a time, okay?
我简直不敢相信竟然你知道该怎么做
I can't believe you know how to handle this.
嗯 我在角色扮演里玩过一次妇产医生
Well, i played the abortion doctor in a Hell House once.
- 哦 棒啊 - 如果这有用的话
- oh, cool. - If it helps,
我是一个受训过的助产士
I'm a trained midwife.
- 加勒特 你在录像吗? - 是啊 为了小博
- Garrett, you're filming this? - yeah, for Bo.
- 我觉得他会想知道 - 好吧
- I figured he'd want to see it. - All right.
大家能不能回避一下?
Can everyone else back up?
这是很私人的事
This is a private moment.
你做的很好
You're doing great.
- 我就在这 - 不好意思 小姐
- I'm right here. - excuse me, miss.
防晒霜和防晒乳有什么区别啊?
What's the difference between a sunblock and a sunscreen?
来了来了! 孩子要出生了
This is it! the baby's coming!
好的 很棒
All right. That's nice.
我喜欢这个 这个很好
I like that. i like that.
是的 就是这样 伙伴们
Yeah, this is it, guys.
来了 就是此刻
It's coming. this is the moment.
宫缩停止了
The contractions stopped.
啊  那就...
oh. That's...
我猜是布拉克斯顿希克斯收缩  这是假临产
Braxton hicks, i guess. it's false labor.
我觉得我得穿上我的裤子了
I guess it should put on my pants now.
超级商店
第一季 第十一集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
公司的目标演习
The company's targeted maneuvers
也是这个任务的一个直接反映
are also a direct reflection of its mission.
翻译  Harrio Oliver
这里写着 “云九商店的任务书是
It reads, "Cloud 9's mission
翻译  Davion 巴西
另一篇文章
statement is another article
上面写着..." 好的 不好意思
creates a..." okay, i'm sorry.
夏安? 你还好吗?
Cheyenne? You okay?
校对  苹果酒  糖糖 苏沐秋
我没事
I'm fine.
我只是...
I just...
时间轴  喻心黄速西子耶 马路边
宝宝压住我的肺...
The baby's compressing my lungs...
搞得我呼吸很困难
and making it really hard for me to just take a full breath.
特效  福娃  喻心黄速西子耶
压制  冰岛
- 但我没事 不 你看起来不怎么好
- But i'm okay. - No, you're not okay.
昨天在店里
You almost gave birth to your child
你差点就把孩子生出来了
In the store yesterday.
是 伙计 我多希望跟这个一样好的借口
Yeah, dude, i wish i had an excuse
用来逃班
This good to ditch work.
我不能回家
I can't go home.
我要凑工时 你知道么?
I need the hours, you know?
为了我的小女儿
For this little girl.
- 他踢你了? - 不 我只是...
- Did it kick? - no, i just...
我摸了下自己这里 然后我尿了一点
I touch myself here and it makes me pee a little bit.
太搞笑了
this is ridiculous.
她不需要因为怀了小孩而折磨自己
She shouldn't have to kill herself just to have a baby.
你们知道吗? 在每个发达国家
Did you guys know that in every other first-world nation,
带薪产假是必须的
Paid maternity leave is just automatic?
哇哦 不 不 你可不能
Whoa, no, no, you are not
把我们弄上另一个新闻里面
gonna forward us another article.
哦 哦 那真是很棒
Oh! oh, that was a big one.
从这个位置看 这种会议更难熬了
These meetings are worse from up here.
我们每个人都可以正式休一天病假
Each of us would officially take a sick day,
但我们仍然过来上班
But we'd still come in,
然后我们打Cheyenne的卡
And we'd clock in as cheyenne,
这样她就可以休一天假 但仍然有工资拿
So that she can take the day off, but still get paid.
是的
Right.
然后她晚点再付给我们?
And she can just pay us back later?
Cloud 9去年赚了超过十亿美金
Cloud 9 made over a billion dollars last year.
我们为什么不让他们付产假的工资呢?
Why don't we just ask them to pay for maternity leave?
哦 你想要打给公司然后问他们吗?
Oh, you want to just call corporate and ask them?
听起来很简单啊
That sounds easy.
值得一试 不是吗?
It's worth a shot, isn't it?
我的意思是 我们能损失什么? 他们最多拒绝嘛
I mean, what's the worst they can do, say no?
员工服务处
Employee services.
嗨 我是来自1217店的艾米 杜班诺夫斯基
Hi, this is Amy Dubanowski from store 1217.
我们有个员工就要生孩子了
We have an employee here who's about to have a baby,
我在想我们是否可以让她
and i was wondering if maybe we could get her
休带薪产假呢?
some paid maternity leave.
不好意思 我们不给带薪产假的
I'm sorry, we don't offer paid maternity leave.
别就这么放弃
Don't just give up.
嗯 我们有些人
Well, some of us
在想也许你可以改改这个政策
were wondering if you could change that policy,
因为我们真的很希望这样
because we really want it.
嗯 这个我们真的不能负责
Um, that's just not something we offer.
好的 但是 这个
Okay, but is it, like, a conversation
咱们现在进行的谈话...
You guys are having...
因为我知道其他大公司都提供带薪产假的
Because i know other big companies do offer it.
一般来说 他们的职工在工会里
Typically, their employees would be in unions.
转接中 请勿挂机
Transferring now. please hold.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你为什么这么说?
Why would you say that?
- 说什么? - 你好 艾米
- Say what? - Hi there, amy.
我是职工关系部的副部长 杰瑞米
This is Jeremy, vice presidet of employee relations.
嗨 我不是很清楚
Hi. i don't know exactly...
麻烦你稍等一下 艾米
Do me a solid and hang tight for one second, Amy.
这什么情况? 我也不知道
- What's happening? - I don't know.
请等候格雷格听电话
Please hold for Greg.
谁是格雷格? 为什么我们要找格雷格?
Who's greg? why are we getting Greg?
- 我是格雷格 - 嘿 我是杰瑞米
- Go for greg. - Hey, it's Jeremy.
我这里有法律部的蕾贝卡还有1217店的艾米
I've got Rebecca from legal and Amy from store 1217,
他们有关于关于工会的问题
where we've got that union problem.
- 不不不 - 不
- Oh, no! no. - No.
我们在说带薪产假的事
We were talking about maternity leave
然后有个烦人的人说到了"工会"这个词
and somebody very annoying mentioned the word "union."
哇哦 不如我们深呼吸冷静一下吧
Whoa, let's just all calm down, take a breath,
从窗台旁退回来
Step back from the ledge.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
这没窗台
No, there's no ledge.
- 我们没人说工会的事 - 不不
- Nobody's talking about unions. - no way.
而且也没人罢工
And nobody's going on strike.
请稍等
Please hold.
我们现在接上了霍华德
Yeah, hi. okay, you've got Howard,
苏 雪莉 基思 吉列尔莫...
Sue, Cheryl, Keith, Guillermo...
- 好多人啊 - 蕾妮 还有艾伦也在这
- That's so many people. - Renee, and Alan here.
喂
Hello.
- 你好啊 - 好啊
- Hi. - Hi.
好的 坚持住 1217
okay, hang tight down there, 1217.
我们明早第一时间
We're sending someone down to you
就会给你们派个人过去
First thing tomorrow morning.
- 不用啊 - 这样安排不错吧?
- No. - Good stuff?
不 等下
No, no, no, no, wait, wait.
你不用这么做的
You don't have to do that.
再见 真是愉快的谈话
Bye. Amazing talk.
我怎么不知道你姓度班诺维斯基?
How did I not know your last name is Dubanowski?
各位早上好 喝点咖啡
Morning, everyone. grab some coffee.
这里还有甜甜圈
Help yourself to a doughnut hole.
你看到这里在发生什么了 对吧?
You see what's going on here, right?
公司察觉到了危机 所以他们派了条鲨鱼过来
Corporate smells trouble, so they send in a shark.
一个又大又摆动着的鸡巴
A big, swinging wiener.
让他自己先显摆一番
Have him swing his wiener around a little.
给我们一点小小的处罚
Give us a slap on the wrist.
一个又大又摆动着的鸡巴对我们指关节的轻敲
A little rap on the knuckles from a big, swinging wiener.
这将会是漫长的一天
This is gonna be a long day.
是啊
Yeah.
来自1217分店的伙伴们 大家好
Hello, 1217.
我的名字叫史蒂芬
My name is Steve.
有没有人知道我是谁?
Does anyone here know who I am?
- 我知道 工会破坏者 - 好回答
- I know. a union buster. - Good one.
我会记住这个回答的 真幽默
I'm gonna remember that one. Funny.
不 我是一个劳动关系咨询师
No, I am a labor relations consultant.
云九不是一个反工会的公司
Cloud 9 isn't anti-union.
工会对于那些
Unions are great for people
公司从不听取员工意见的人是很好的
Whose companies don't listen to them.
但是不管你的顾虑是什么
But whatever your concerns are,
你永远能在任何时候给予他们权力来团结在一起
You can always bring them right to corporate any time.
棒呆 我们确实是有一些问题
oh, great. some of us did have some concerns
然后我想向你问一问
That I wanted to ask you about.
我特别愿意听一听
and i want to hear about them.
但是首先 我们需要找一些乐子 对吗?
But first, we're gonna have some fun. yeah?
你们都拿了咖啡和甜甜圈了嘛?
Has everyone gotten some coffee and a doughnut hole?
现在我们要做一些角色扮演的练习
Now we're going to do a little role-playing exercise,
然后我绑架了你们的经理格林来帮我一个忙
And I’ve roped in your manager, Glenn, here to help me out.
好吧 谢谢你
Um, okay. thank you.
你将会扮演一个工会的组织者
You're gonna play a union organizer,
然后你要试着让我来把工会卡给签了
And you're gonna try to get me to sign this union card.
好吗? - 没问题
Okay? - Sure.
- 好吧 - 你好
- All right. - Hi, hello.
- 我的名字叫史蒂芬 然后这个吧工会... - 好吧
- My name's Steve, and the union... - Okay.
你知道么? 你做的很好
You know what? you're doing great.
但是我的名字是史蒂芬
But my name is Steve,
所以这可能会把其他人搞糊涂
So that might be a little confusing for everyone.
所以再选一个名字
So maybe pick another name.
好吧 没问题 抱歉
Okay, sure. sorry.
- 不好意思我有些紧张 - 你做的很好啊
- Sorry I’m just a little nervous. - You're doing great.
- 你好啊
- Um, Hi.
我的名字是...史蒂芬
My name’s...Steve.
好吧
All right.
在这出戏中我是史蒂芬 好吗?
I'm gonna be the Steve in this scene, right?
- 所以... - 好吧
- So... - All right, all right.
你是史蒂芬
You're Steve.
好的
Okay.
- 对不起 我没弄懂 - 你做的很好了
- Sorry, misunderstanding. - You're doing great.
- 好吧
- okay. all right.
你好 史蒂芬
Hello there, Steve.
我的名字是...
My name's...
史蒂芬
Steve.
讲真 你知道么
Literally, you know what?
全宇宙任何一个别的名字都行啊
Any other name in the entire universe?
史蒂芬
Steve.
好吧 这样吧
Okay, you know what?
让我们给格林一点掌声
Let's give glenn a round of applause.
你做的很好了
You did great.
不要担心 好的
No worries. All right.
也许我们可以找一个不同的志愿者
Maybe a different volunteer.
那个穿着紫色polo衫的怎么样?
How about you with the purple polo?
谢谢你 迪娜
Thank you for that, Dina.
迪娜现在是我们的工会组织者
Dina's gonna be our union organizer,
然后她将试着去让我把工会卡给填了
And she's gonna try to get me to sign this union card.
让我们看迪娜是如何应对挑战的
Let's see if Dina is up for the challenge.
好吧 嗨 想不想参加工会?
Okay. Hey, how'd you like to join a union?
不 不用了 我不需要
No, thanks. I don't need to.
云九公司已经听取了我的顾虑
Cloud 9 already listens to my concerns.
我真的认为签署加入工会
I really think it'd be in your best interests
是对你自己最好的选择
to sign this card.
请不要强迫我
Please don't bully me.
我不需要花钱让别人替我说话
I do not need to pay someone to speak for me.
看到了? 我把她嘴给闭上了
See? I shut her down.
这就是两个例子
Those are two examples.
不要打断我
Stop interrupting me.
要么你签了这张卡 要么你小命不保
You will sign this card or i will choke the life out of you.
迪娜算是影帝了 对吧?
And the oscar goes to Dina. Right?
看 她扮演的这个角色真是...
See, she was playing a character there that was...
- 我才没在扮演角色
- Oh, I’m not playing a character.
是我迪娜在跟你 工会破坏者史蒂芬说话
This is me, Dina, talking to you, union buster Steve.
我现在心情很不美丽
I'm in a dark place right now,
而且 公平地说 我没什么可以损失的了
And quite frankly, i have nothing left to lose.
所以你要么签了这张卡
So you will sign this card,
要么我会在停车场等你
Or I will be waiting for you in the parking lot
然后在灯光找不到的地方 撺紧我的手
At the end of the night, where i will wrap my hands
卡住你的鸡脖子
Around that tiny chicken neck of yours
然后紧紧的盯着你的眼睛
And stare deep into your eyes
然后静等生机熄灭
while I watch the lights go out.
我们还是休息一下吧
Let's take a break.
要不我分给你一点?
You want some of mine?
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
嘿 哥们
Hey, man.
只是想让你知道 我知道除了史蒂芬以外的名字
Just want to let you know, I know names besides Steve.
大家字幕组
你当然知道
Of course you do.
我还知道格林 还有...
There's glenn, and there's, um...
史蒂芬
steve.
谢谢你的时间
Thanks for your time.
现在事实呈现给你们了
Now you have the facts.
怎么选择利用好它们是你们的事了
How you choose to use them is up to you.
- 谢谢大家 - 谢谢 天哪
- Thank you. - oh, thank you, god.
我懂的好吗
I know, right?
不好意思 抱歉
Excuse me, sorry.
大家对不起啊 但是你之前说
Sorry, guys, but you had said earlier that maybe we
我们可以在会议的最后提出一些建议?
could voice some concerns at the end of the meeting?
谢谢你了啊 乔纳
Thank you, Jonah.
- 我很抱歉 很抱歉 - 当然了
- I’m sorry. i'm sorry. - Absolutely.
- 云九向来广听民意 - 很好
- Cloud 9 has an open door policy. - Great.
我们几个人在讨论有没有给员工
So a couple of us were talking about the possibility
提供带薪产假的可能性?
of paid maternity leave for the employees?
你知道 云九一向支持提供福利和关怀
You know, Cloud 9 is devoted to supporting the welfare
给我们所有宝贵的员工
and values of all of its workers.
好了吗? 谢谢
Okay? Thanks.
你能不能讲的再详细一点?
Could you be a little more specific?
- 我喜欢这个 - 好
- I love this. - Great.
我们喜欢这种激情和正直
We love this kind of passion and integrity
使云彩更加多元与完整
that adds to all the colors of the cloud.
好吧 但是你其实什么都没说啊
Great, but you're not actually saying anything.
那是因为我在真诚的聆听啊
That's because i'm truly listening.
你知道我才想到了什么吗?
You know what i just realized?
我们给你们提供了足够的甜甜圈
We have enough doughnut holes for all of you
所以每个人都可以再多吃一个了!
To have one more each!
是不是? 快去吃吧 伙计们
Right? Dig in, everyone.
大家啊 甜甜圈在这放了几个小时了
Guys, they've been there for hours.
这会议真特么搞笑
That meeting was such a joke.
他们压根不会为夏安做一点事
They're not going to do anything for Cheyenne.
他们压根就不在乎
They don't care.
你现在才发现啊
You're just realizing that now.
这家公司连甜甜圈都不给
This company, that wouldn't even spring for full doughnuts,
只提供缩小版的面包球
just doughnut holes
这不仅仅是夏安的事
It's not just about Cheyenne.
这关乎到我们所有人
It's about all of us.
我们是让这个公司运行下去的人
We're the people that make this company run.
他们得学会对我们好一些
They need to start treating us better.
就像马特奥... 昨天你
Like mateo... what was it you were
抱怨什么玩意来着?
complaining about yesterday?
记得吗?
Remember?
恩
yeah.
- 为什么我们的顾客都长得这么丑? - 嗯哼 没错
- Why are our customers so ugly? - mm, yeah.
不是这个 他们怎样把我们工时控制在40小时以下
No, how they keep us under 40 hours
这样他们就不用给我们奖金了 是这件事
So they don't have to give us benefits?
哦 对 是的 这个也很操蛋
oh, right, yeah. that sucks too.
我五年都没长过薪水了
I haven't had a raise in five years.
- 看到了吧 - 我就说说而已
-There you go. -I mean, not to complain.
对不起 我又瞎逼逼了
Sorry, i'm babbling.
- 对不起 - 不不不
- Sorry. - No, no.
我们就应该为自己发声
We should be speaking up about this.
好吧我们好像没什么谈判的筹码
It's like we don't have any leverage.
你知道吗 也许我们真该成立个工会
You know, maybe we should form a union.
嘿 冷静点
Okay, calm down.
伙计 你不能让这里的每个人都
Dude, you can't get everybody
同意加入公会
here to agree to join a union.
我们甚至在夏季烧烤的主题上都统一不了
We couldn't even agree on a theme for our summer barbecue.
最后成了"哈利波特海下的八十年代阿拉伯之夜"
Ended up being "1980s Arabian nights under the sea harry potter."
所以你就想一点改变都没有吗?
So you just want everything to stay exactly the same?
这太荒唐了!
That's ridiculous!
如果罗莎·帕克斯当初...
What if rosa parks...
懂了
Got it.
扯远了 我的错
Amped up, sorry.
瞧瞧他 这个大码裤先生
Look at him. Mr. Big Pants.
就一直等着我们出糗
Just waiting for us to slip up
这样他就能再来教训我们了
so he can bring hammer down.
我觉得他就是在喝咖啡而已
I think he's just having a coffee.
拉倒吧
Oh, come on.
大码裤小子
Mr. Big Pants.
到处甩着他那又臭又长的小鸡鸡
Just swinging that big old wiener around.
你这话我没法接
and we're back to wiener.
给你
Here.
有人让我把这些拿给你读
I was told to hand you these to read,
这也是我工作的一部分
'cause that's my job now.
负责送文件
I drop off pieces of paper.
看呐
Look at that.
搞定
Nailed it.
- 嘿 你想读一次吗? - 我?
- Hey, you want to read one? -M e?
就算这件事并不是上司的工作
I mean, it's not exactly like being the boss,
但确实有点上帝之声的感觉
But it has sort of a voice of god quality about it.
因为大家都得听你讲话
Everyone has to listen to you.
注意啦 云九顾客
Attention, Cloud 9 shoppers.
包装纸和礼品袋
We are offering a 10% discount
现在打九折
On all wrapping paper and gift bags.
心动不如行动
Come check out this heavenly deal.
怎么样 很爽吧?
Feels powerful, right?
哦不 我只是第一次觉得我的声音
no, i just never realize my voice
竟然这么弱小
Had just such a weak, tinny quality.
不不 你嗓音超赞
No, you've got a nice voice.
不 你成功地侮辱了我
No, you've succeeded in humiliating me.
“你成功地侮辱了我”
"You've succeeded in humiliating me."
就这样 我声音听起来就这样
That's me. that's what i sound like.
你听起来一点都不像...
You don't sound anything like...
别再让我说话了
Stop making me talk.
真他妈像一场噩梦
This is a nightmare.
-“联合意向” - 没错
-“Intent to unionize." -Yep.
“国际环卫工人兄弟会”
"international brotherhood of sanitation workers."
我网上抄的
I printed it off the web.
我会划掉然后填上云九的
I'm gonna cross that out and write “Cloud 9."
伙计 今天早晨开的那个又早又长的会
i'm sorry, were you not at that extremely long
你到底有没有听啊?
and early meeting this morning?
当然了 有啊 但它只让我确定了一件事
Yeah, i was, and all it did was confirm
除非我们做点什么的话
That nothing is gonna change
那就是这里一切都不会改变
around here unless we change it
如果你真的想帮夏安的话 这就是唯一的方法
If you want to help Cheyenne, this is the way to do it.
不 你脑子进水了吧
No, this is stupid.
但是值得一试啊
It's worth a shot.
不！这一切都是因为最一开始你说
No! That's what you said about calling corporate
要给公司打电话的
In the first place.
- 不是什么鬼都能试 - 很抱歉
- Not everything is worth a shot. - I’m sorry.
我只是不习惯当我身边的人需要帮助的时候
I'm not the kind of person who just stands by doing nothing
而我却坐视不管
while people around me need help.
好了 好了 我懂了
Oh. okay. yeah, i get it.
你那小脑瓜里正幻想着
You have an image of your head
你领导所有的工人
of leading all the workers out
进行一场愚蠢的大罢工
In some dramatic walkout,
然后你就能碾压那个男的了
And you're gonna bring down the man.
我跟你讲
But let me tell you something.
现实是人们的工作岌岌可危
Real people's jobs are at stake.
你把我形容成一个愚蠢的空想家
I am so sick and tired
而把自己看作是有智慧的实干家
of being painted as the stupid idealist
这种做法真是又恶心又无聊
while you get to be the smart, pragmatic one.
我没说你蠢
I’m not saying you're stupid.
我只是说你压根不知道真是世界是什么样的
I'm saying you don't know how the real world works.
不知道世界是什么样
There's a difference between
和没胆子做出改变
not knowing how the real world
完全是两回事好嘛
works and not having the guts to do something about it.
- 哦 呵呵 - 她在生孩子吗?
- Oh, okay. - Is she having her baby?
- 是 我觉得是 - 我们得...
- Yeah, i think so. - We should...
对
Yeah.
你把地板弄得乱七八糟的
You've left your insides all over the floor,
现在竟然还把孩子带来上班
And now you've brought your child to work.
- 格林 你在干嘛... - 不
- Glenn, what are you... - no, no, no.
我是认真的
I mean it.
你被停职了
You're suspended.
四周
For four weeks.
带薪
With pay.
- 但... - 你还狡辩?
- but I... - But?
你想让四周变六周吗?
You want to make it six weeks?
好啊 决定了 就六周
Okay, fine. bam. six weeks.
带薪停职
Paid suspension.
还要继续狡辩吗 小盆友?
You want to keep going, missy?
不了
no, I’m good.
很好
good.
我准备好走了
I’m ready to go now.
- 谢啦 - 拜拜 小口琴
- Thank you. - Bye, Harmonica.
拜
Bye.
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
请进
Yeah.
嗨 格林
Hey, Glenn.
我想说
I just wanted to say that what
你刚才做的太帅了
you did back there was awesome.
谢谢
Thank you.
别担心 你都不会注意到咱们少了夏安
Don't worry. you won't even notice Cheyenne is gone.
我不担心
I’m not worried.
以后就轮不到我担心了
It's not my problem anymore.
你在...你在说什么?
What are you...what are you talking about?
嗯 我被炒了
yeah, they let me go.
- 什么? - 嗯
- what? - yeah.
他们不能就这么开除你
- They can't just fire you.
你整个人生都奉献给这个地方了
You've given your whole life to this place.
没事的 我还是会整天在店里闲晃的
Don't worry, i'll still be in the store all the time.
只不过是以客人的身份罢了
Just as a customer.
我会问你诸如 "嘿 牙线在哪儿啊?"
I'll say stuff like, “Hey, can you tell me
之类的蠢问题
where the dental floss is?"
不过也有可能不问啦 因为我知道它们在哪儿
Well, probably not, cause I already know where it is.
除非你决定要换位置放
Unless you decide to move it.
什么? 你在说啥?
What? What are you talking about?
他们让我推荐个人
they asked me if i wanted to make
作为我的继位者
A suggestion for my replacement,
而你是最了解这家店的人
and nobody knows this store better than you.
我拒绝 我不做
um, no. i'm not doing it.
那他们会让别人来做的啊
Then they'll just get someone else.
我不在乎 格林 我不要拿你的工作
I don't care, Glenn. I’m not taking your job.
艾米 等等!
Amy, wait!
到了明天 总有一个人会坐在那个椅子上
Someone is going to be in that chair tomorrow.
而那个人必须得好好照顾我们全体的员工
And that person has to take care of everyone in this store.
与其让一个陌生人掌权 我宁愿让你来
I'd rather that person be you than some stranger.
艾米 你是一个领导者
Amy, you're a leader,
而这些人需要一个能引领他们的人
And the people here need a leader.
你能做到吗?
Can you do that?
天呀 夏安 她太可爱啦
Oh, Cheyenne, she's awesome.
嗯
yeah.
小风琴
Harmonica.
我可以
I can do it.
那个 你能先别为我的孩子做洗礼了吗
Oh, could you not baptize my baby?
啊 抱歉抱歉
Oh, i'm sorry.
乔纳
Jonah.
都是我的习惯
Force of habit.
你肯定又要说我做错了
You think I’m doing it wrong,
格伦 没关系的
Glenn, if it's okay,
但如果我这么摆的话
But if we stack them five wide and low,
我明天 估计要晚十分钟到了
I might just be, like, ten minutes late tomorrow.
这些就没那么容易被推倒了
They're less prone to toppling.
夏安 你明天真的不用来了
Cheyenne, you are not coming to work tomorrow.
但是我需要我的工资呀
I need the money,
- 怎么了? - 他们把格林开除了
- What's wrong? - They fired Glenn.
而且据说我明天那时就止血了
and they said i would mostly be done bleeding by then.
- 什么? - 对 所以说
- what? - yeah, so, um...
但是你应该和孩子待在一起呀
But you should be with the baby, though.
关于那场罢工
About that walkout.
没关系的 我妈妈会照顾她的
It's okay. my mom can watch her.
马特奥
Mateo.
我会留点我的衣服给她
I'm gonna leave her with some of my clothes,
格林被开除了 我们要罢工
Glenn got fired. we're walking out.
你要加入吗?
Are you coming?
这样他就能先熟悉我的气味啦
So she can start to learn my smell.
当然
yeah.
夏安 我不允许你这样做
Cheyenne, this is unacceptable.
抱歉 想弄出青绿色那种效果
Sorry, was doing a teal and green story.
你让我们大家都不能专心工作
You've distracted us from our work.
加勒特 所有的员工
garrett, all the employees
都要早退因为大家要罢工
are leaving early because they're staging a walkout
因为格林被开除了
because Glenn got fired.
没问题 哥们 这理由行啊
Sure, man, that works.
你还没把卡还我呢
You still have my credit card.
人呢?
Hello?
天哪 你们不用这样做的
Oh, no, no. you guys do not have to do this.
好吧 我知道了 我理解
Okay, you know what? I understand
你们因为格林的事情很不开心
That you're upset about Glenn.
我知道了也理解 不不
I know and i get that. no, no.
拜托 公司爱你们的啊
Come on. Corporate cares.
当然了 格林
Sure, Glenn.
给自己弄个新车吧 就一次
Help yourself to a brand-new car, just this once.
工作进展也很好
Job's going great.
不会出现什么问题的
What could possibly go wrong?
能管用吗
Is this gonna work?
我也不确定
I don't know.
但值得一试 对吧?
But it's worth a shot, right?
现在干嘛?
So what now?
大家注意
Attention, please.
注意听
Listen up.
我想说两句
I have something i'd like to say.
我知道你们都很不安
I know you're scared.
这是个重大时刻
This is a big moment.
但不要担心
But rest assured
云九没了你们也会很好的
Cloud 9 will be fine without you.
得了吧
come on.
总之 我会给你们的智能卡消磁
Anyway, I’ve demagnetized your keycards,
然后会把工资邮寄给你们
And you will receive your final paychecks in the mail
你们工作服的费用将从工资里扣除
With the costs of your vests deducted from them.
这并不针对任何人 祝你们好运
Nothing personal. I wish you all luck,
我得去管理我的商店了
But i've got a store to manage.
谢谢
Thank you.
这个消息真的让我振作了起来
This really cheered me up.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140
大家字幕组
祝你们今天棒棒哒
Oh, and have a heavenly day.
大家字幕组